# **Rhonda Easterday**

Mansfield, OH (567) 241-6678

# Technical Project Manager

Rhondaeasterday530@gmail.com LinkedIn

# **Summary**

Remote IT project manager proficient in Jira software, Agile methodologies, and Agile Development. With over 10 years of budget management, Microsoft Excel, and marketing analysis from restaurant management, I enjoy using Jira software. Creating a backlog and subtasks with a timeline is essential to a successful project, I feel it is a perfect tool for agile development.

## **Skills**

**Technical:** Jira software, Dev-ops, Microsoft Excel, PowerPoint, Agile methodologies, HTML, Safe

Methods: Budget management, project management, SWOT analysis, strategic analysis, data analysis, agile development

# **Recent Projects**

# Project Charter | Project link

- Created a mockup charter of a web design company to house all project objectives, requirements, and communication
- Included budget estimate and detailed cost worksheet
- Prepared in Google documents

### Requirements Management | Requirements Management

- Developed a management plan that outlined a process for changes, accountability for project milestones, and user acceptance responsibility
- Gathered requirements for the project and assigned tasks and accountability
- The way requirements activities will be planned, tracked, and reported

# Experience

#### **RESTAURANT MANAGER**

Mansfield, OH

# Steak & Shake

October 2017 - April 2020

- Overseen employee work in the front and the back of the house to ensure compliance with company, policies, regulations, and food safety guidelines
- Managed staff of 45 to 50 people
- Increased revenue by 10%
- Produced monthly reports detailing sales trends and forecast

#### MACHINE OPERATOR

Mansfield, OH

September 2017 - September 2019

## Mancan Inc.

- Produced piece rate to ensure completion date is on time
- Inspected parts to ensure quality
- Reworked and repaired any product not meeting standards

#### **GENERAL MANAGER**

Youngstown, OH July 2006 - March 2016

#### Taco Bell

- Managed P&L to stay in the 95 % to 110%
- Increased revenue 11% in 6 months
- Achieved Plaque for highest C.O.R.E audit, for the year average 99%

### Education

### CERTIFICATE, THINKFUL

April 2021

## **Technical Project Management**

- Agile Methodologies, User Research, Estimation Techniques, Project Management, Agile Development, and StrategicAnalysis
- 12 week intense boot camp, 60 hours per week